Anthony Shaloub

2098 Sutter St, Apt 204, San Francisco, CA 94110 shalouba@mail.com (815) 487-3982

Highly skilled DevOps engineer with 10+ years of experience. Knowledge of software development technologies and processes backed by a graduate degree in computer science from Stanford University and multiple certifications. Proven track record of helping organizations enhance their software products and increase revenue.

Key Skills

- Project management
- Ansible
- Git
- Ruby
- Peri
- Python
- •
- C++

Professional Experience

DevOps Engineer

Dropbox, San Francisco, CA j October 2016 - Present

- Provide monitoring and reporting for DevOps environments
- Use Git for managing source code and version control
- Export data to relational databases to generate business intelligence reports
- Collaborate with other software developers to build development pipeline and deployment processes

DevOps Engineer

Smart Security Inc,, San Jose, CA I November 2010 - September 2016

- Worked with a team of three other DevOps engineers to identify areas for improvement and implement solutions
- · Developed monitoring and alert notification tools
- Spearheaded project for improving deployment process, resulting in an 80% reduction in manual work
- · Presided over a period of 30% revenue growth

Education

Master's Degree in Computer Science

Stanford University Stanford, CA, September 2006 - June 2010

Certifications

- ♦ CompTIA Linux+, 2018
- ♦ Red Hat Certified Specialist in Ansible Automation, 2016